Inventory to the Records of the Albert Schweitzer Chair in the Humanities 1965-1984 RG 21.1
New York University Archives
- Series VI: Lecture Series Recordings
  - Titled Reels: Language and symbolic action, D. Sherak for Ralph Ellison (1 reel), undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Titled Reels: NYU I (1 reel), undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Titled Reels: NYU II (1 reel), undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Titled Reels: 3 untitled reels, undated (Box 13, Folder 14)